Shido, what's in here?
Is it a date?
Tell me!
Upon Toka's arrival in this strange new world,
she was immediately faced with a challenge.
She could choose to fight against the appetite
of her growing curiosity,
or feed it generously with love.
And today, Shido's wallet is also feeling conflicted.
Tell me!
She shines in waves
the aftermath of waves
appear in waves
and in the dark universally
One more time
is된
with some light
and will Racine
into her example
that Mahogany
I don't know why I can't believe it
I can't believe it in my hands
I'm not sure why I can't believe it
I'm still afraid of the love that I can't believe it
If another room somebody is here
The star that we've ever met
THANK YOU! PLEASE COME AGAIN!
please come again here you go
is this a test am i about to fail no it's for you stop drooling
was this one of those date things no spread okay is that another name for date i don't understand
how something so delicious can't be called a date you can call it one if you want to
fascinating even though this was delicious it's still not good enough to be called a date
and so the mystery continues
there's one not quite oh he's perfect where'd he come from is this one
you don't want to do that why are you stopping we were saving us i'm not there's nothing to
save us from no one is trying to hurt us
look mama see i threw it in the trash all by myself wow what a good boy you are
what about right now this moment is this a date not really but you're getting closer dates are
complicated matters
look that thing over there looks yummy
oh the world are you still hungry am i cray or is that shida with a new girl oh my gosh does that
mean he's cheating on tonomachi that's so lame that woman i know she's a spirit but there's no
no spatial quake sergeant origami reporting a zero six one three need an observation device immediately
i can't believe humans eat such amazingly delicious things oh hey toka what happened after you left
yesterday same thing as usual i swing my sword around some i blast the artillery in the end my body
disappeared naturally like it always does disappeared yes i go to a world different from this one it's a
dark space once i get there i just fall asleep so you mean when you wake up you come here well i don't
wake up on my own it's more like by force and it has nothing to do with what i want i'm just pulled
here usually anyway by force then spirits don't cause spatial quakes on purpose they must just be
accidents by usually you mean today was different how would i know please tell me look that might
actually be the reason there wasn't a spatial quake today you're too persistent besides i have important
things to do like find more food come on wait i should have brought more money it looks like she's a
98.5 match that's way too high to be a coincidence of course but why is she here she isn't wearing her
spirit armor right now if we want to attack this is it think about where you are you know we can't
afford to be reckless what kind of place is this uh an expensive one i don't know what that means i'm
going in no wait hold on well if it isn't shito mochi what do we have here that's some hot action
how did you manage to pull that kind of tail without me knowing about it huh i'm a little jealous yeah a lot
has happened lately i guess whoa and straight off the top of the shelf it's cool man my lady's got
some pretty expensive taste too check it out right his virtual girlfriend listen i want to help you
someone gave me these tickets but i think they'll impress your fancy new girlie and help you score
later you're welcome in advance let me know how it goes see you later bud
how are you today reina what what are you doing here checking on princess we have to make sure we're
not at risk of another spatial quake she's been waiting for you right over there over here shito why
are you so late sorry what's up kitten you ready to order this looks so good but so does that one
i wonder which of these two is the date hey if you guys can't decide i have a suggestion for you but how
about this what does that one come with what does that one come with whoa should be called what's with
all this oh no thank you it tastes so outrageous it must be a date what are you trying to pull here
coterie thank you works too we're pulling out all the stops to help you score because i'm awesome but
we also have some business to discuss as soon as you guys leave i need you to head south of the station
but what for that's just a residential area okay then i trust you've got this now let's get this date
started checking ai analysis use shop type e-59-63 e-59-63 roger
open the main gate
what's that let's eat it it looks so yummy no you can't eat them well you can but not those wow
they even have red ones they're so fast yeah the red ones are three times as fast as the others
don't know why they'd be here though the heck is all that congratulations
what is going on here you two are this shopping arcade's 100 000 visitors so we have a special gift
for both of you everything you eat here today will be free congratulations thanks but i don't get
it i've never seen one of those before wait toka come back here nice work kawagui all right fried food
team get ready for service fish cake and shaved ice team approach customers noodle team why was the
delivery late do you think we're gonna be okay shin and toka are moving in glad to see we're all ready
and prepared for action speak for yourself
the signal's jammed origami can you hear me i've managed to squeeze mobilization orders from the higher
ups meet us at point 101 roger that yummy i can't get over the throne what's that it looks amazing
oh so does this give me slow down don't rush as much as you want it's free how the hell did this
happen shito i'm having fun are you huh this has been such a great day and i'm having a wonderful
time here but i'm worried i'm the only one you seem upset are you mad at me no way of course i'm not mad
at you are you sure i'm positive in fact i'm in a great mood i've just had a lot on my mind is all
promise you're having a good time best time ever i really hope you're telling the truth i am i swear
i'm glad we came here today there's so much food we have to try let's get the most we can out of the
state yeah let's great come on okay wherever you need me to go i'll follow
congratulations you two you won the grand prize two tickets to dream park redeemable anytime
woo i don't know what that means but it sounds like fun it's the most fun you'll ever have what's
this you've never been that's unheard of you've got to take her right now
game park wow look how beautiful this place is what an adventure what kind of things can we do in
here well i don't know do it do it do it hey i have an idea let's not go in there okay i don't
agree you told me that we could go wherever i wanted today shito do you think i'll learn what
a date is behind those doors something tells me that's very possible but i don't think it's a good
idea today i'm not ready to go yet how am i supposed to learn if you won't let me experience
these things origami where are you what's happening the time to meet has passed currently surveying the
movements of the target send an emergency arming device to point zero eighty eight one hundred seven
i can't believe i'm seeing this why didn't he bring her in to do the deed this isn't the first time
you've failed with that tactic is it kawagaway fact established and acknowledged classic shito he always
insists on doing everything in a proper order what's that rain strange there weren't any rain clouds in the
vicinity oh well maybe it's for the best where did you bring me is this the secret base of the mecha mecha squad
of course not don't worry
why can't i get you you unruly chicken shito tell this thing to cooperate i told you this is a
really tough one you have to have a strategy and yelling through the glass doesn't work fine then how
this one should be easy it's sticking up that's not the one i want i want the chicken okay well maybe
there's another one like it somewhere i can get you whichever prize you want come on hit one
maybe that one i've got it listen closely i'll use this button over here you use the one on your
side there let go when i give the signal it's worth a shot
wait for it wait for it wait for it
now let it go toka
chicken hold on it still hasn't dropped yet
i'm so sorry that was totally my fault i didn't give good instructions
drop the chicken please drop it why won't you listen to me shito and i worked so hard on this drop it
please please it's okay i'm begging you drop it you have to please
we did it
question what method do those use to transform actually trains don't transform what so they use
fusion well they do connect to each other oh wow thank you i had so much fun today good me too
thanks for coming i am a little disappointed that we didn't get to explore dream park oh it's totally
overrated if you say so but shito the day is almost over and i still didn't see a date
can you tell me what one is like a date is just when a girl and a boy go out and have a good time
together you can't actually see one oh that makes sense well in that case i would say we had a
wonderful date today uh sure
i like dates they're nice not good i can't believe i'm seeing this a spirit shows up without
a spatial quake and then connects with a human boy permission to shoot miss not yet still waiting
to hear from the top this is a very unusual situation no one's been evacuated i'll just have
to wait and see point alpha here what happened what we've got permission to shoot all the humans
were very kind today no one tried to kill you did they i knew you'd be okay yeah you're right i never
knew the world was so kind so much fun and so beautiful i love it here and now i understand why
the mecha mecha squad is after me because whenever i appear in this world something bad happens
i ruined something beautiful i ruined your world that's not true so listen i've been thinking and
it's better if i don't exist anymore don't say that we're fine there was no spatial quake today was there
you didn't ruin anything yes but that doesn't mean there won't be one the next time i appear
once i go back and fall asleep i won't be able to control myself fine then i guess you just can't go
back have you ever even tried just once just try staying here even if i did there are so many things
i don't know about this world i'll teach you whatever you don't know then i'd need food and
then a place to sleep what if something happens we're not prepared for i'm going to take care of you
if something comes up that we need to deal with we'll deal with it are you sure am i even allowed
to be here is it okay for me to be alive in this world yes it is you're the only one who would say
that to me humans like the mecha mecha squad they don't want to risk it they don't want something as
dangerous as mean you i don't care about them even if everyone else rejects you it doesn't
change the fact that i accept you and i don't want you to leave take my hand that's the only job you
have right now distance 512 15. wind direction 40.8 wind speed 0.4 temperature 24 degrees rh
52.8 we're all clear what are you doing
we're all clear what are you doing
origami origami origami come in origami
shito
i thought maybe if you were here for me it would be okay it might be hard but i'd be able to do it
with you by my side i can get through anything when i'm with you but it doesn't matter it's no use
you're gone you're gone now i'm on my own this world has rejected me
okay
It's not a wreck!
That's a bomb!
Hovenhove!
How dare you!
How dare you reject me!
No way.
Origami, retreat immediately!
Support troops, where are you?
Origami, do you read me?
So it was you.
You're the one who did it.
You killed my only friend.
And with him, my soul.
Just admit it.
Yes. I killed Shiro Itsuka.
Kill her.
She must pay for what she's done.
She must die!
It doesn't look like a pulse or heart rate is registering for Shiro.
The special quick alarm is going off. This can't be good.
Resident evacuation is still at 7%.
We're lucky there aren't many houses nearby.
But at this rate, the whole town will be decimated within minutes.
If she were a knight, she would have earned a passing break.
But if she gets herself killed as a princess, then she's obviously not worth our concern.
Excuse me, Commander. What have we heard about Shiro?
Oh, I wouldn't worry too much about him.
My brother won't be finished off by something like that.
There it is.
Where am I?
Commander, what do we do now?
I already told you. Even if Shiro dies, he'll be able to start a new game.
So what the heck are you dragging ass for?
Get down there and recover him immediately.
No one else is able to stop her.
It has to be him.
That's right. The method we've decided to save for last.
I did it.
I killed someone.
I'm like them. The spirits.
You're the same.
We must end this.
Dad. Mom. I'm sorry.
Shiro, I promise to avenge you.
What? He's alive!
Shiro, is it really you?
Yeah. Yeah, I think it is.
Thank you. Thank you for coming back.
We're coming back!
You're crying. Everything's okay now, but...
Toka? What the heck is that?
I accidentally am she's helping to help.
I have to find someone to release it.
No, hold on. You definitely can't do that.
Then what should I do?
It's already reached its critical state.
Shiro, can you hear me?
Now is the time to use that method I taught you earlier.
It's the only way you'll be able to save her.
All right, Toka. Listen to me.
We have to kiss now, okay?
We what?
Uh, never mind. Forget it.
I'm sorry. There has to be another way.
No, I just don't know what a kiss is.
Huh?
Teach me and I'll do it.
Um, okay, it's where we put our lips together and then we...
I'm so sorry. They told me this was the only way I could reverse it.
Just don't let me go.
I'm not ready for you to see me naked yet.
Shiro...
Uh-huh?
Will you, um, take me out on another date sometime?
Of course. Anytime you want to.
Need to get my tears.
Off you, you do it.
Thank you.
Catch me,予感だけは気にした
触れられない扉がある
その手でそっと落として
鍵を外し
お願いでまた
次回予告
Kids, I'd like to introduce you to our new transfer student
I'm Toka Yatsugami
I'm so excited to meet all of you
I'm so excited to meet you